A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the President, Senior Advisor, Office Files of Frank DeGiovanni FA1876
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject files, 1990-2016; 2; 26.91 Cubic Feet 67.5 document boxes: 53.5 letter boxes and 14 legal boxes
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit September 1998 Program Review (Box 54, Folder 709)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Community and Resource Development unit (CRD) September 1998 Program Review Session (Box 54, Folder 710)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Community and Resource Development unit (CRD) September 1998 Program Review and Retreat (Box 54, Folder 711)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) September 1999 Program Review (Box 54, Folder 712)
  - Community Reinvestment Act (CRA) papers, 1997-1999 (Box 54, Folder 713)
  - Community Reinvestment Act (CRA), 1995-1999 (Box 55, Folder 714-715)
  - Community Reinvestment Act (CRA), 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 716)
  - Affinity Groups travel budget, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 717)
  - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF), 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 718)
  - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) Fiscal Year 1999-2000 Operating Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 719)
  - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) November 1999 Annual Meeting, London, England (Box 55, Folder 720)
  - Adhiambo Odaga Program Officer Memo - Development Finance and Economic Security and Environment and Development, West Africa Office, 1999-2000 (Box 55, Folder 721)
  - Nick Menzies Program Officer Memo - Environment and Development and Development Finance and Economic Security, East Africa Office, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 722)
  - Stephen J. McGurk Program Officer Memo - Economic Security Project, Beijing, China Office, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 723)
  - Anthony Tillett Program Officer Memo - Development Finance and Economic Security and Community Development, Santiago, Chile Office, 2000-2001 (Box 56, Folder 724)
  - Michael Conroy Program Officer Memo - Environment and Development, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 725)
  - Akwasi Aidoo Program Officer Memo - Human Rights, West Africa Office, undated (Box 56, Folder 726)
  - Chris Page Program Officer Memo - Enterprise Development, undated (Box 56, Folder 727)
  - Ingrid Faulhaber Program Officer Memo - Development Finance and Economic Security, Mexico and Central America Office, 1999-2000 (Box 56, Folder 728)
  - Jane Rosser Program Officer Memo - Development Finance and Economic Security, India and Nepal Office, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 729)
  - Community Foundations Leadership Program Conference on Program Related Investments (PRI), April-May 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 730)
  - Making Workforce Development Work: Streamlining and Informing? Or Training and Building Bridges - Brooking Institution policy brief, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 731)
  - Community Foundations Leadership Program Conference on Program Related Investments (PRI), April-May 1992 (Box 56, Folder 732)
  - National Association of Community Development Loan Funds (NACDLF) April 1993 Conference (Box 56, Folder 733)
  - Juhudi Kilimo, 2009-2011 (Box 56, Folder 734)
  - Lobbying flow chart, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 735)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2003 reserve requests, 2001-2002 (Box 56, Folder 736)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2005 reserve requests, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 737)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2004 reserve requests (Box 57, Folder 738)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2003 reserve requests, 2002-2003 (Box 57, Folder 739)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2004 reserve requests, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 740)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2003 reserve requests (Box 57, Folder 741)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2001 reserve requests, 2000-2001 (Box 57, Folder 742)
  - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit Fiscal Year 2005 reserve requests, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 743)
  - National Community Stabilization Trust (NCST), 2008-2009 (Box 57, Folder 744)
  - Consumer protection - Testimonies and articles, 2004-2009 (Box 57, Folder 745-746)
  - Meetings with Pablo Farias, 2002-2005 (Box 57, Folder 747)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED), 2007 (Box 58, Folder 748-749)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED), 2006-2007 (Box 58, Folder 750-751)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED), 2006 (Box 58, Folder 752)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) presentation for Ford Foundation Trustees, undated (Box 58, Folder 753)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) Universal Model, 2005-2007 (Box 58, Folder 754)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) policy meeting, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 755)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) budget, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 756)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED), 2005-2007 (Box 59, Folder 757-758)
  - Better Than Cash Alliance (BTCA) June 2015 Executive Committee Meeting (Box 59, Folder 759)
  - The Mott and Ford Foundations' Children's Savings Accounts March 2014 Strategy Session (Box 59, Folder 760)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation Program February 2014 Global Learning Event, Paris, France, 2009-2014 (Box 59, Folder 761)
  - United States Financial Diaries January 2014 Advisory Board Agenda (Box 59, Folder 762)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation Program August 2013 Ethiopia Pilot Field Trip, 2009-2013 (Box 59, Folder 763)
    File contains digital media
  - The Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation Program: Linking safety nets to financial services in Ethiopia, undated (Box 59, Folder 763)
  - Heifer International, undated (Box 59, Folder 764)
  - Mott Foundation - Children's savings accounts assessments, 2012-2014 (Box 59, Folder 765)
  - Asset building - Miscellaneous reports and meeting materials, part 1, 2011-2015 (Box 59, Folder 766-767)
  - Asset building - Miscellaneous reports and meeting materials, part 2, 2012-2015 (Box 60, Folder 768-769)
  - Credit scoring, 1994-1998 (Box 60, Folder 770)
  - Harvard University Joint Center for Housing Studies - Towards a Targeted Homeownership Tax Credit, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 771)
  - September 1999 Washington D.C. trip - Self-Help and Fannie Mae (Box 60, Folder 772)
  - 1999 Columbus, Ohio trip - Self-Help and Fannie Mae, 1998-2000; File contains three still images (Box 60, Folder 773)
    The file contains three photographs. The photographs are of Ford Foundation president Susan V. Berresford (photo – Ben Russell, February 1998), Fannie Mae Chairman and CEO James A. Johnson, and Self-Help CEO Martin Eakes (photo – Jennifer Warburg/Impact Visuals).
  - Self-Help, 1998-1999 (Box 60, Folder 774-775)
  - Self-Help and Fannie Mae progress reports, 1998-1999 (Box 60, Folder 776)
  - Self-Help, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 777)
  - Global Equity Fund, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 778)
  - Global Equity Fund, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 779)
  - Global Equity Fund - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 780)
  - Seed Capital Development Fund (SCDF) Phase 2, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 781)
  - Seed Capital Development Fund (SCDF) Feasibility Study, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 782)
  - Ford Foundation United States program strategy, 2015 (Box 61, Folder 783)
  - Ford Foundation November 2014 Worldwide Meeting, New York City, New York - Notes (Box 61, Folder 784)
  - Ford Foundation regional planning process and strategy development, 2014 (Box 61, Folder 785)
  - Ford Foundation April 2014 Directors and Representatives Meeting, 1992-2014 (Box 61, Folder 786)
  - Ford Foundation Philanthropy Working Group July 2014 Kickoff Meeting (Box 61, Folder 787)
  - Ford Foundation July 2014 Directors and Representatives Meeting on Themes (Box 61, Folder 788)
  - Wayne Fawbush - Monthly reports and other documents, 2012-2013 (Box 61, Folder 789)
  - Amy Brown - Monthly meetings, 2012-2013 (Box 61, Folder 790)
  - Kilolo Kijakazi - Monthly meetings and statistics, 2012-2013 (Box 61, Folder 791)
  - Inclusive Economies thematic area design team, 2015 (Box 61, Folder 792)
  - Ford Foundation program thematic area materials, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 793)
  - Ford Foundation program thematic area materials, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 794)
  - Ford Foundation program thematic areas materials, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 795)
  - Ford Foundation program thematic areas materials - Correspondence and notes, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 796)
  - Program strategy - Macro trends discussion, 2014 (Box 62, Folder 797)
  - Strategic planning summer 2015 - Thematic areas and Lines of Work Statements (Box 62, Folder 798)
  - Ford Foundation United States regional program strategy, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 799)
  - Ford Foundation United States regional program strategy, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 800)
  - Ford Foundation United States regional program strategy, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 801)
  - Ford Foundation United States regional program strategy, 2015 (Box 62, Folder 802)
  - Ford Foundation United States regional program strategy, 2014-2015 (Box 63, Folder 803)
  - Ford Foundation Program Related Investments (PRI) Sector Research Project - Presentations, 2015-2016 (Box 63, Folder 804-805)
    Restricted – Open in 2027
  - Ford Foundation Executive Leadership Team Meeting Regional Inequality Exercise, 2015 (Box 63, Folder 806)
  - Ford Foundation Investment and Social Justice May 2014 Convening (Box 63, Folder 807)
  - United States National Advisory Board on Impact Investment (NAB) 2.0, 2015 (Box 63, Folder 808)
  - Ford Foundation Impact Investing January 2015 Convening, 2014-2015 (Box 63, Folder 809)
  - Impact investing strategy and development, 2015 (Box 63, Folder 810)
  - Ford Foundation Impact Investing January 2015 Convening - Notes (Box 63, Folder 811)
  - Impact investing consultants - Monitor Deloitte, part 1, 2014 (Box 63, Folder 812)
  - Impact investing consultants - Monitor Deloitte, part 2, 2014 (Box 64, Folder 813-814)
  - Correspondence Records on National Credit Union Foundation's (NCUF) Proposal to the Ford Foundation December 2002-February 2004 (Box 64, Folder 815-816)
  - Rural Livelihoods Practitioners Learning Group (RLPLG), 2007 (Box 64, Folder 817)
  - Mountain Association for Community Economic Development (MACED) - Theory of Change, 2007 (Box 64, Folder 818)
  - Assets Program November 2004 Meeting, Chennai, India (Box 64, Folder 819)
  - Frank DeGiovanni and Suzanne Siskel March 2007 visit to Hanoi, Vietnam (Box 64, Folder 820)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP) November 2004 Meeting, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 64, Folder 821)
  - Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office - Gender, Racial, and Ethnic Justice (GREJ) outcomes, 2016 (Box 64, Folder 822)
  - Ford Foundation Middle East and North Africa (MENA) Regional Office strategy development, 2016 (Box 64, Folder 823)
  - Creativity and Free Expression (CFE) strategy, 2016 (Box 65, Folder 824)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Regional Office strategy, 2015-2016 (Box 65, Folder 825)
  - Inclusive Economies, Quality Work and Economic Security (QWES) strategy, 2016 (Box 65, Folder 826)
  - Vacant Properties Strategy May 2009 Meeting (Box 65, Folder 827)
    The date of the meeting is misprinted at the front of the file.
  - Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office Inclusive Economies outcomes, 2016 (Box 65, Folder 828)
  - Gender, Racial, and Ethnic Justice (GREJ) outcomes - Working documents, 2016 (Box 65, Folder 829)
  - Thematic Area and Regional Office Team Instructions and Strategy Development Guides, 2015 (Box 65, Folder 830)
  - Ford Foundation Mexico and Central America Regional Office strategy, 2015-2016 (Box 65, Folder 831)
  - Thematic Area and Regional Office program strategy - Drafts and working documents, 2015-2016 (Box 65, Folder 832-833)
  - Equitable Development strategy development, 2016 (Box 65, Folder 834)
  - Youth Opportunity and Learning (YOL) strategy, 2016 (Box 65, Folder 835)
  - Civic Engagement and Government (CEG) outcomes, undated (Box 66, Folder 836)
  - Impact Investing Sector Scan, 2015-2016 (Box 66, Folder 837)
  - Program strategy high level outcomes for Program Vice Presidents/President Darren Walker Review, 2015 (Box 66, Folder 838)
  - Ford Foundation Jakarta, Indonesia Regional Office strategy, 2016 (Box 66, Folder 839)
  - Internet Freedom strategy outcomes, 2015-2016 (Box 66, Folder 840)
  - Andean Region regional program strategy, 2015 (Box 66, Folder 841)
  - Thematic Area and Regional Office program strategy development - Drafts and templates, 2015 (Box 66, Folder 842)
  - Regional strategy outlines, 2015 (Box 66, Folder 843)
  - Youth Opportunity and Learning (YOL) strategy, 2016 (Box 66, Folder 844)
  - Ford Foundation Lagos, Nigeria West Africa Regional Office strategy development - Drafts, 2016 (Box 66, Folder 845)
  - Ford Foundation Johannesburg, South Africa Southern Africa Regional Office strategy, 2015-2016 (Box 66, Folder 846)
  - BUILD, 2016 (Box 66, Folder 847)
  - Ford Foundation Nairobi, Kenya Eastern Africa Regional Office strategy, 2016 (Box 66, Folder 848)
  - Community Development Innovation and Infrastructure Initiative (CDIII) report, 2000 (Box 67, Folder 849-850)
  - Self-Help/Ford Foundation/Fannie Mae Initiative Summit VIII, December 2006, Washington D.C. (Box 67, Folder 851)
  - Ford Foundation, Self-Help, and Center for Community Capital (CCC) June 2009 Summit (Box 67, Folder 852)
  - Ford Foundation, Self-Help, and Center for Community Capital (CCC) February 2008 Research Meeting (Box 67, Folder 853)
  - Saving for Educations, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) April 2008 Initiative Report (Box 67, Folder 854)
  - Building Economic Security over a Lifetime (BESOL) March 2011 Grantee Convening (Box 67, Folder 855)
  - Center for Community Capital (CCC) Community Advantage Panel (CAP) Research Plan, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 856)
  - Consultative Group to Assist the Poor (CGAP)-Ford Foundation Graduation Program July 2012 Pilot Meeting, 2011-2012 (Box 68, Folder 857)
  - Self-Help December 2009 Summit, 2000-2009 (Box 68, Folder 858)
  - Center for Community Capital (CCC) Community Advantage Panel (CAP) August 2013 Research Meeting (Box 68, Folder 859)
  - United States Financial Diaries Advisory Board September 2012 Meeting (Box 68, Folder 860)
  - United States Financial Diaries Advisory Board September 2012 Meeting (Box 68, Folder 861)
  - Future of Work strategy, 2014-2015 (Box 68, Folder 862)
  - Gender, Racial, and Ethnic Justice (GREJ) Women and Girls programming strategy, 2015 (Box 68, Folder 863)
  - Program strategy development - Design Team Phase 2, 2015 (Box 68, Folder 864)
  - Program strategy development - Office of Communications edits to Communications Template, 2015 (Box 68, Folder 865)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) March 2005 Semi-Annual Progress Reports (Box 68, Folder 866)
  - Ford Foundation April 2005 Presentation - Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED) Priorities, Organizational Strategy, and Financial Plan, 2004-2005 (Box 68, Folder 867)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) April 2005 Advisory Board Meeting, San Francisco, California (Box 68, Folder 868)
  - February 2006 Learning Visit - Development Finance and Economic Security Portfolio in Mexico briefing book (Box 68, Folder 869)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) October 2008 Initiative Report (Box 69, Folder 870)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) Year 1 Impact Evaluation, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 871)
  - HomeOwnership Program Year 1 Progress Report - Not Just Buying a Home, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 872-873)
  - Ford Foundation Program on Social Protection in Asia, 14-17 May 2006, Bangkok, Thailand (Box 69, Folder 874)
  - Masters Pagoda Vietnam, March 18, 2007 (from Charles Bailey to Frank DeGiovanni) (Box 69, Folder 875)
  - Paths to Learning: Successful Innovations in Rural Microfinance in Latin America and the Caribbean, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 876)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Cognitive Interviewing Report, circa 2007; File contains digital media (Box 69, Folder 877)
  - Saving for Education, Entrepreneurship, and Downpayment (SEED) for Oklahoma Kids Cognitive Interviewing Report, May 2007, RTI International (Box 69, Folder 877)